architecturaldesigns.com 2009-06-19

# House Plans & Home Designs from Architectural Designs - Privacy Policy

| House plans, floor plans and home plans to suit your every need |   
| 

|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
|  **[House Plans](http://www.architecturaldesigns.com/)** |  |  **House  Plans Include** |  |  **About  Us** |  |  **Services** |  |  **Contact  Us** |  |  **FAQs** |  |  **Affiliates** |  |  **Builders** |  |  **[Site Map](http://www.architecturaldesigns.com/sitemap.asp)** |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
| **[Search Results](http://www.architecturaldesigns.com/house-plan-73035hs.asp) ** |  | **[We Are](http://www.architecturaldesigns.com/about/weare.asp)** |  | **[Prices](http://www.architecturaldesigns.com/about/price.asp)** |  | **[Terms](http://www.architecturaldesigns.com/about/terms.asp)** |  | **[Copyright](http://www.architecturaldesigns.com/about/copyr.asp)** |  | **Privacy  Policy** |  |   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
---  
  |  | **Privacy Policy**  
---  
**Security of Information Transmissions:**  
**Orders:** All personal information, including your credit card information, that you provide on the order form at this Website is secured by the highest level of encryption. In other words, the information is scrambled when it is sent from your system until it reaches the bank we use for credit card transactions. We use [Verisign® Payment Processing](http://www.verisign.com/) to manage the security of all credit card transactions. Your Web browser should indicate when a document is secure and encrypted for transmission.  
**Other Email** : Other email sent to and from our site is NOT secure. Therefore, we ask that you do not include confidential information such as credit card numbers in email. For this reason, we do not include your credit card information in the order acknowledgement sent to you via email if you order online.  
**Information We Obtain from Visitor Browsing:**  
Architectural Designs creates and maintains a "cookie" on your system. This cookie contains no personal information. It is used to assist your search for house plans and to let us know how you found our web site.  
If you use this site to order products from Architectural Designs, you will need to give us certain personal information just as you would if you were communicating with us in person, by fax, by mail or by telephone. The same internal protections that we employ in the maintenance of information received via these channels is applicable to the information we obtain via the Internet.  
If you send us an email message, we may retain the content of the email, your email address, and our response.  

---  
|  |  [House Plans](http://www.architecturaldesigns.com/) |  Contact Us  |  Copyright  |  Privacy Policy |  [House Styles](http://static.architecturaldesigns.com/) |  [Site Map](http://www.architecturaldesigns.com/sitemap.asp)   
  
****Architectural Designs :: 57 Danbury Road :: Wilton, CT 06897  
USA & Canada 1-800-854-7852 or 1-877-229-2447 :: International 262-521-4596  
Fax 1-203-761-8600 :: Email: [info@architecturaldesigns.com](mailto:info@architecturaldesigns.com)** ** |  |
